# **Dima Pidko**

# React Full-stack Dev.

ABOUT

I am 22 years old student at V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University and get skills on Udemy platform. My first attempts at writing code were back in school, then i realized that i liked solving various problems with different levels of complexity and this became the starting point in the world of IT. After entering the university in 2019, i began a deep study of programming, which i continue to study to this day.

EDUCATION

#### Bachelor, 105 - Applied physics and nanomaterials

V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University

2019 - 2023, Kharkiv

# Web-Developer, JavaScript + React/Redux

uDemy

2023 - present

EXPERIENCE

### Chatter APP ( pet project ) writing on TypeScript

React dev, 2024 - Now

Here I learned how to work with WebSocket. I improved my knowledge in HTTP requests and also improved my work with the MySQL database. I also used Redux

here. GitHubLink

# Business card site (Hopster RestoPub)

React dev, 2024 - Now

Here i created single page application for RestoPub.

I learned to work well with the DOM tree. There is a complete understanding of working with state using Redux, as well as the Redux tool-kit. **GitHubLink** 

#### Technical Task for IT school (pet project)

React dev, 2024 - Now

props. GitHubLink

Here I created an application to join an IT school and improve my knowledge in Web development. The project turned out to be not so difficult, but some points made me think. When creating the project, I consolidated my knowledge of React / react-router-dom / styles module / RESTAPI / OOP principles. Strengthened knowledge in component life cycle / component state / passing functions through

pidkodima@gmail.com +380668370182 Kharkiv

## **Industry Knowledge**

React / Next.Js
JavaScript / TypeScript
Node.Js / Express.js
HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS
GIT / GitHub
Understanding SOLID / DRY
/ OOP

#### Languages

Ukrainian (native)
English (Intermediate)

#### Social

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmytro-pidko-0ab8512ab/

https://github.com/ DimaPidko

https://t.me/ditsmon